did I forget
student versus Guru who will win so I'm
going to be challenging one of my top
students on a two-week Challenge and
whoever has the best results at the end
of the week will win ten thousand
dollars like how's this guy gonna beat
me I literally taught him how to trade
for those of you guys that don't know
who Jordan is Jordan has been calling my
signals for the past month and a half uh
because you guys already know I'm a
swing Trader day trader so I'll probably
send one or two trades a week Max so I
kind of needed help to keep the chat
active so I hit up Jordan he kept
blowing me up literally blowing me up in
the DMS with a bunch of results I'm like
yo you're dope come to my chat call
signals did it for about a month or two
now my signals are officially closed if
you guys want to know more about that
just go hit up his chat and in these two
weeks I'm going to be challenging him
because he literally tried me he said yo
I'm a better Trader than you so I'm like
all right let's put it to the test so
we're going to be documenting our
journey for the whole entire two weeks
and whoever has the best results at the
end of it will owe each other ten
thousand dollars let's get it all right
so Jordan just pulled up don't mind the
thing on the floor within construction
at the top so
this is Mr this is Mr Jordan right here
so get get to know Jordan yo what's good
guys
in this challenge I know I'm gonna be
Alex because I just know look at the
results from the signals so what makes
you think you're gonna be Jordan in this
challenge
I mean I literally taught this guy out
of trade like you could be my top
student that's cool but I really taught
this guy out of trade how do you feel
according to this challenge
I feel ready to take a free vacation how
are you feeling getting going into this
challenge with him I mean honestly
probably the only con that I have is
that he's a scalper I'm a swing Trader
they traded but easy spell not gonna lie
what's your game plan I'm talking this
challenge
my game plan is the same game plan I've
been following for three years that's
kept me profitable you must have a game
plan a specific game plan to follow this
instead of forget all right so this day
one of the challenge it is February 19th
as you guys can tell this is where we're
going to start the challenge so I'm
going to take you guys through the whole
entire week of how I trade and Jordan's
gonna do his part so today we're going
to go on Sunday swings which is what I
do every single Sunday with the students
and I give them the top three top four
pairs that I'm going to trade for the
week that have the highest probability
trades of going in our favorite right so
these are trades that are gonna
basically get us to win this challenge
so let's get it all right what's up guys
so it's Sunday night it's literally the
first day of the challenge so I'm
anticipating price to pull back into
this area right here to give me a cell
movement to take me down to this area
down here so let's see what happens now
when New York opens
all right guys so it is day two in the
challenge room we're about to take this
trade together on my million dollar
account right now that I currently have
from rocket so there's my million dollar
account from rocket so we're literally
gonna take this trade together right now
actually come so so I show you guys the
trade that I got going on all right so
right now this is USD card so USD CAD on
The Daily time frame we are obviously
bullish and then on the weekly time
frame we are bullish as well you can
tell we have a very clean bullish weekly
engulfing Candlestick as you guys can
see we have three time frames in sync I
only look at I only like to take a trade
if we have a minimum of three time
frames in sync so as you can tell the
four hour has retraced perfectly to
retest this four hour structure level
here and we've had a beautiful four hour
bullish engulfing you go down to the
lower time frames lower time frames
you've had the shift retest of the EMA
and I just sent it right now literally
right now in my Discord and I'm like USD
card is looking good we already got
somebody that I think they're already
probably inside of it so we're literally
gonna take this trade together the
Candlestick just closed so a million
dollar account on Rocket so I'll come
here I'll go to USD card I already went
over here to my effects book position
size calculator and I calculated the
wrist so so risking two percent it's
gonna be a hundred Lots so this is like
extremely trippy so like I'm not gonna
do 107 lots I'm just gonna round that
off to 100 Lots so we're gonna go to USD
CAD come over here we're gonna do a
hundred Lots
does it even let me
so 100 lots and then my stop loss is
gonna be bro you guys need a stop loss
my stop loss is going to be
413.
all right so as you guys can tell we got
the 100 Lots in on USD CAD uh I have a
stop loss no take profit I get asked all
the time why don't put it take profit
because that would defeat the purpose of
set and figure out you want to make sure
your trade goes up as high as it can you
don't want to cut your profit short you
want to cut your losses short you don't
want to cut your profit short so let's
see how this trade takes out I'm gonna
be chopping it up with the guys in the
Discord all right so this is where we
are in the trade currently you guys saw
that we just took it together so right
now it's probably a thousand dollars in
profit we're so every single time I take
a trade on this account I'm down like 2K
like right away obviously it's a big
account so it doesn't feel it
um but now we literally just said and
forget and we just right now at this
time at 10 o'clock I'll probably go hit
the gym take a nap and let's just see
where the Knight takes us all right so
Alex to be cooking up some heat because
as you guys can see it's later on Monday
night and exactly what I told you guys
was going to happen today is what
happened I ended up sending this trade
in the signal room and we are currently
up almost one to four times our risk
price uses M5 Supply mentioned with a
high of date and you can see when Asia
opened up that's literally where the
volume came in from
all right so while Alex was asleep last
night I was able to catch a cell on your
USD as you guys can see it's Tuesday
morning and I was able to catch the cell
right before London giving me almost uh
three times my risk so yeah let's see
what Alex is up to
say that me and the students were always
laughing at like these type of jokes
because it happened you're getting
You're Gonna Get Wicked out it's part of
the process there's no way of avoiding
it just kind of says how it's like
perfectly but what we're not gonna talk
about it I'm gonna see uh if I get back
in into the same trade I'm just waiting
for a nice engulfing I'm waiting for
like another clean entry signal right
now I'm eyeing another trade but I will
keep you guys updated I want to make up
for this trade uh that I gave you guys
it was a loss part of trading it happens
we're zero and one for the week down two
percent we just needed a quick one to
two one to three and we're back up so
stay tuned wow I was literally about to
send the trade to you guys and it just
shot up right now if you guys can tell
we just got back in so it's kind of
crazy because the original trade that I
was in yesterday literally got Wicked
out by nothing so if I would have maybe
made this stop loss a little bit bigger
we would have still been in the trade
but it's okay it happens so now I just
got in on the trade again and it's still
valid we just got Wicked out on the
whole entire move but wow I was about to
send to you is to get the trade
um if we do happen to have any pullback
on these time frames in the 30 or 15
minute time frame make sure to get in
this is going to be a solid trade setup
just like that boys if I want to close
this trade we'll be right back at break
even but that defeats the purpose
because we got a one to five versus
rewards so if this trade hits take
profit we're looking at 100K trade
oh my God
[Music]
all right so today's Wednesday yesterday
I did not take a trade during New York
session but as you guys can see we're
literally a minute away from market open
on Wednesday and I'm anticipating price
to pull back into this area right here
to continue a bullish movement to this
previous low of date so let's see what
happens guys all right so a little does
Alex know that I'm kicking kicking it
but in the challenge today
today's trading days on Euro USD and I
think to celebrate it's only right to
get a new car it's something that I've
had in mind for a while and
apart from being a mentor in the charts
he's literally a mentor in life and he's
always telling me to force myself to
level up and do better so I think I'm
gonna surprise him with me getting a new
car and show them the profits as well
all right guys we actually did it I
actually pulled it off now I just got
the keys and everything is final it's
pretty insane the power of trading you
guys saw how it was just a thought this
morning and I was able to make it a
reality by the end of the day that's
literally the power of trading for you
guys I promise you guys this happened
didn't happen overnight like this took
time
literally years and a lot of Blown Blown
accounts but I promise you guys if you
don't give up and you have a vision for
something and you hustle every day and
you put in the work like nothing's gonna
stop you only you could stop yourself
and definitely like this would not be
possible if it wasn't for Alex like I
promise you I would not be standing here
with this car if it wasn't for Alex all
right so you guys just saw this show
that happened on Tuesday we literally
called the trade live on my Instagram to
the t wait this out to the T and I
managed to get in so I was gonna like
film the whole thing on my phone because
say about something with me but I'm like
you know what I gotta Focus I gotta get
back in this trade I gotta get the
community back to win so all you guys
saw was just clips of the Instagram
there but so we basically got Wicked out
by one pip um and then we got back in we
made three times our risk so we're up
about like 45k on that one trade alone
so right now we're gonna go hit the gym
uh before London and then we'll catch
you guys back at the office all right so
this day for the challenge and you guys
already see how we're doing this week I
have no idea how joining is going right
now all right guys so we're about to put
up on addicts right now and surprise him
with the car let's see his reaction
foreign
yo I'm outside I got something to show
you what yo that I just pulled up come
outside I got something to show you
yo what is this yo I told you I had
something to show you
it's mine
yeah bro you always telling me to level
up and force myself to do better so I I
figured out I'd surprise you but I can't
believe
[Applause]
yo yo yo yo yo yo
what is going on here man
yo what you doing
is this is this where you're hiding you
about yeah that's what I told you I had
a surprise me before
so it's not mine it's your car no it's
my car
yeah so what so why why event where'd
you get a vet dude I missed throwing a
manual party oh it's manual yeah it's
manual oh
you're gonna let me drift this job nah
of course of course
Donuts whatever you want to do yeah bro
no Santa forget me
foreign
New York session but that's all good
here we are four minutes before Market
opens and I'm waiting to take a cell
position coming from this area here if I
don't get my entry confirmation from
this area then I'll definitely take a
cell from this area coming up here all
right so my analysis played out just how
I said price pulled back to this area of
supply and then we're able to catch this
cell giving us almost a one to four I
secured a one to three and this cell was
caught in the signal group so it is day
five of The Challenge and I'm of about
4.2 percent right if I'd have not gotten
whipped out earlier this week by that
Miss and more of a pip I would have been
about six to seven percent in profit so
for me I usually Target 2.5 a week so if
I'm up 4.2 percent for the week that to
me is a dub with only one single trade
so I haven't taken any trades today
but I'm a five percent so simple math
tells me that you owe me 10K I don't
know yeah yeah so this is what I'm
thinking I technically do right so so
you surprised me with the car we made
more profits to me you're kidding how
many trades did you take I took four
okay so you took four trades yeah so
then you lost two you won two one two
okay exactly I think what we should do
is we should do another week so we
should do a part two where we actually
Journey more and get into more details
of the traces I miss some of my trades I
saw you missed like filming some of your
trades so I mean are you down to double
yeah what I mean so if I no if you win
I'll pay you 20K and then if I win all
you gotta do is give me 10K so I'll take
double the risk if you're down you don't
like give it down yeah sounds good done
yeah all right so if you guys are down
to see a part two just drop comments
down below say in part two or whatever
you guys want to comment because if we
do a part two this can give me more of
Leverage in a way so I can take more
aggressive trades and actually be more
active I only took one single trade
versus four right so it shows you that
both strategies work it's just the type
of entries and the type of way you
approach yourself drop a comment uh down
below if you guys want to see a part two
oh by the way I have a three day boot
camp that is also known as 3333 right
I've been feeling something special
about this one it's the third time I've
ever done a three-day boot camp you guys
want to know just more about it click
the link below so you guys could be the
next Jordan let's get